<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Buddies App</string>
    <string name="wish">Happy Friendship Day!</string>
    <string name="splash_name">Welcome to my Buddies App!</string>
    <string name="surp">Surprise!</string>
    <string name="dedicatn">This is dedicated to all my \'yaar\'. To friends who became really special and important part of my life since past few months.
    \n \nThe random posts in #random channels by @nalayak surely brings smile on our faces in this fast-paced lives.
    \n \nThe introduction challenge in the #introductions channel through which we know the vastness of Google Udacity Scholarship and the challenges which each one of us have crossed.
    \n \nThe never ending challenges by all moderators in different channels that give us a head start and a big flight to meet deadlines in a fun and easy way.
    \n \nThe list can go on and on. Here are some special ones whom I had a chance to be in contact with and who really inspires me to learn without limits.
        \n \nThank you so much for being with me always :p\n
    </string>

    <string name="name1">akshit.udacity</string>
    <string name="desc1">Akshit Jain is the Student Experience Lead at Udacity. He always comes up with great ideas and surprises for everyone.
        He is a really good friend and mentor alike who is always ready to help.
    </string>

    <string name="name2">Geeta.fend</string>
    <string name="desc2">Geetanjali is the student moderator of #git_github channel on Slack. She always comes up with new challenges and tasks for everyone.
        She is a very good speaker and is confident in whatever she does.
    </string>

    <string name="name3">karthikeyan.mws</string>
    <string name="desc3">Karthikeyan is the student moderator on Slack. He has amazing skills and is always ready to help no matter the time.
    </string>

    <string name="name4">lakshit.and</string>
    <string name="desc4">Lakshit is a very dedicated person towards his goal. He has amazing skills and is always doing something or the other.
        He is always available if I get stuck anywhere and provides instant and great solutions.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ded">DedActivity</string>

</resources>
